<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><Manifest CSUVersion="1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="CSUManifest.xsd">
    <UpdateID>1.1.3</UpdateID>
    <OwningChannel>AdobePreviewCC-1.0.0</OwningChannel>
    <TargetBuildType>2</TargetBuildType>
    <DisplayName default="en_US"><en_US>Adobe Preview CC</en_US>
        <de_DE>Adobe Preview CC</de_DE>
        <fr_FR>Adobe Preview CC</fr_FR>
        <it_IT>Adobe Preview CC</it_IT>
        <ja_JP>Adobe Preview CC</ja_JP>
        <es_ES>Adobe Preview CC</es_ES>
        <sv_SE>Adobe Preview CC</sv_SE>
        <zh_CN>Adobe Preview CC</zh_CN>
        <zh_TW>Adobe Preview CC</zh_TW>
        <nl_NL>Adobe Preview CC</nl_NL>
        <ko_KR>Adobe Preview CC</ko_KR>
        <nb_NO>Adobe Preview CC</nb_NO>
        <da_DK>Adobe Preview CC</da_DK>
        <fi_FI>Adobe Preview CC</fi_FI>
        <pl_PL>Adobe Preview CC</pl_PL>
        <cs_CZ>Adobe Preview CC</cs_CZ>
        <hu_HU>Adobe Preview CC</hu_HU>
        <ru_RU>Adobe Preview CC</ru_RU>
        <pt_BR>Adobe Preview CC</pt_BR>
        <uk_UA>Adobe Preview CC</uk_UA>
        <tr_TR>Adobe Preview CC</tr_TR>
    </DisplayName>
    <Description default="en_US"><en_US>New option to manually check for Wi-Fi devices. Fixed issues with Wi-Fi connections, preview image updating, and color accuracy.</en_US>
        <fr_FR>Nouvelle option permettant de rechercher manuellement les appareils Wi-Fi. Correction de problèmes de connexion Wi-Fi, de mise à jour de l'image d'aperçu et de précision des couleurs.</fr_FR>
        <de_DE>Neue Option für die manuelle Suche nach WLAN-Geräten. Fehlerbehebungen für WLAN-Verbindungen, die Aktualisierung von Vorschaubildern und die Farbgenauigkeit.</de_DE>
        <it_IT>Nuova opzione per cercare manualmente dispositivi Wi-Fi. Correzione dei problemi relativi alle connessioni Wi-Fi, all'aggiornamento dell'immagine di anteprima e alla precisione cromatica.</it_IT>
        <ja_JP>Wi-Fi デバイスを手動で確認する機能を追加し、Wi-Fi 接続、プレビュー画像の更新、およびカラーの正確さに関する問題を修正しました。</ja_JP>
        <es_ES>Nueva opción para comprobar manualmente si hay dispositivos Wi-Fi. Se han corregido problemas relacionados con las conexiones Wi-Fi, la actualización de imágenes de previsualización y la precisión de los colores.</es_ES>
        <sv_SE>Nytt alternativ som du kan använda till att söka efter Wi-Fi-enheter manuellt. Problem med Wi-Fi-anslutningar, uppdatering av förhandsvisningsbilder och färgåtergivning har åtgärdats.</sv_SE>
        <zh_CN>用于手动检查 Wi-Fi 设备的新选项。修复了 Wi-Fi 连接、预览图像更新和颜色精准度的问题。</zh_CN>
        <zh_TW>提供手動檢查無線網路裝置的新功能。已修正無線網路連線、預覽圖片更新和色彩的正確性。</zh_TW>
        <nl_NL>Nieuwe optie om handmatig te controleren op wifi-apparaten. Problemen verholpen met wifi-verbindingen, het bijwerken van voorvertoningen van afbeeldingen, en kleurprecisie.</nl_NL>
        <cs_CZ>Nová volba pro ruční kontrolu přítomnosti Wi-Fi zařízení. Opraveny chyby připojení Wi-Fi, aktualizace obrazů náhledu a přesnosti barev.</cs_CZ>
        <nb_NO>Nytt alternativ for å søke etter Wi-Fi-enheter manuelt. Løsning av problemer med Wi-Fi-tilkobling, oppdatering av forhåndsvisningsbilde og fargenøyaktighet.</nb_NO>
        <da_DK>Ny indstilling til manuel søgning efter Wi-Fi-enheder. Har løst problemer med Wi-Fi-forbindelser, opdatering af eksempelbillede og farvenøjagtighed.</da_DK>
        <fi_FI>Uusi mahdollisuus tarkistaa Wi-Fi-laitteet manuaalisesti. Korjattu Wi-Fi-yhteyksien, esikatselukuvan päivityksen ja värien tarkkuuden ongelmia.</fi_FI>
        <pl_PL>Wprowadzono nową opcję umożliwiającą ręczne sprawdzenie dostępności urządzeń Wi-Fi. Naprawiono problem z połączeniem Wi-Fi, aktualizacją podglądu obrazu i zachowaniem wierności kolorów.</pl_PL>
        <ko_KR>Wi-Fi 기기를 수동으로 확인하는 신규 옵션. Wi-Fi 연결 관련 문제 수정, 이미지 미리보기 업데이트, 색 정확도.</ko_KR>
        <hu_HU>Új opció a Wi-Fi-s eszközök kézi keresésére. Hibajavítások a Wi-Fi-kapcsolatokkal, az előnézeti kép frissítésével és a színpontossággal kapcsolatban.</hu_HU>
        <ru_RU>Новый параметр для проверки наличия устройств Wi-Fi вручную. Исправлены проблемы, связанные с соединениями Wi-Fi, обновлением изображений предпросмотра и точностью передачи цвета.</ru_RU>
        <pt_BR>Nova opção para procurar manualmente por dispositivos Wi-Fi. Corrigidos problemas com as conexões Wi-Fi , atualização da visualização de imagem e precisão de cores.</pt_BR>
        <uk_UA>Доступна нова функція перевірки вручну на наявність пристроїв із Wi-Fi. Виправлено помилки, пов’язані з підключенням до Wi-Fi, оновлені зображення для попереднього перегляду, а також збільшено точність передачі кольору.</uk_UA>
        <tr_TR>Wi-Fi aygıtlarını manuel olarak kontrol etmek için yeni seçenek. Wi-Fi bağlantıları, önizleme görüntüsü güncelleme ve renk doğruluğuna ilişkin sorunlar giderilmiştir.</tr_TR>
    </Description>
    <AffectedChannels><ChannelID>AdobePhotoshopCC2015-16.0</ChannelID>
    </AffectedChannels>
    <InstallFiles><File RIBSBased="1"><Name>setup.zip</Name>
      <Type>1</Type>
      <ExecutableName>Setup/AdobePatchInstaller.exe</ExecutableName>
      <Size>8890266</Size>
      
    <SignatureType>1</SignatureType>
<Signature>NKNQ/FX00IJULP7NNTmGNd4BG3h7kzXxFEe7rhTi2xxNHNOdPrIRfNx0XfhO1mCVucEtC/WR/reKgrq0c0XXj0LkL3khEgMgmdxt0bLAatdJqDmZQN6VDC74J094073fz9Fgh8x+N4IJw7Z0ohv37f4a3I7yQcfMcIKLZTI1q5/rv/FmZEvARYo0upoWsA/zCzwQb3wXwMcWRuGs/XdP/VIhmT+YVclNoj9raPNVTOP/YkFOtN2V+uSDDTjj/ipMoriJ6xPMfkc8/wN+diTGceFjKmvKcBuue8RpQfol9T1DqIJPH20ewGC1SN7hwFRDsfrPbDfsZ0MgZGD0QqjF4aYw5lDtzyL9Lceq9Tk7YNjuNg/zpVSJyE136ZSX8w/2+CIXK2YHK8BN3rdKrr1seb4jrHo9ljwHSJbGKjGYBFbEwomt8V3i8Mj+kwuhLL2sPeadqSbTfAUcugSVWcudkkbDhUukdm9RdrOn5mKK/tBCqpJ/quP2xsN//wAVHPMi</Signature>
</File>
  </InstallFiles>
    <NeedsReboot>false</NeedsReboot>

  
  
  
  
  
  
  <UpdatePayloadID>{27B8946D-664A-4877-A3C9-CE8249CA1D7A}</UpdatePayloadID>
  <OwningPayloadID>{A3B6E381-F2E8-47CD-87B4-96B1E3FF61D3}</OwningPayloadID>
  <ConflictingProcesses/>
</Manifest>